Guide to the Preservation Department, Yale University Library, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Preservation Department records, 1947-2002; Accession 2008-A-165
  - Professional Activities
    - Schedules - Interns, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 805)
    - NEH Training - Education / Communication, 1979-1981 (Box 17, Folder 806)
    - Preservation - III, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 807)
    - Disaster: the Aftermath, 1975-1979 (Box 17, Folder 808)
    - Microform handouts, 1972-1978 (Box 17, Folder 809)
    - Intro: NEH Grant, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 810)
    - Disaster: Preparation, 1976-1981 (Box 17, Folder 811)
    - Final Intern Project - Program Planning, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 812)
    - Interns - Past 1979, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 813)
    - Interns - Present, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 814)
    - Interns - General, 1979-1981 (Box 17, Folder 815)
    - Interns - Next Pres., 1980-1983 (Box 17, Folder 816)
    - Jans Notes, Interns Notes, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 817)
    - no label (NEH Pres. Project), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 818)
    - Collection Condition Survey, misc, 1978-1983 (Box 17, Folder 819)
    - Preservation Survey, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 820)
    - Preservation Interns and Applicants, 1979-1981 (Box 17, Folder 821)
    - NEH - Intern, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 86)
    - NEH - Mailings to Interns (Box 17, Folder 87)
    - NEH Room 508 / Secretary, Administrative Details, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 824)
    - NEH - Storage and Handling, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 825)
    - NEH Training - Disaster, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 826)
    - NEH Training - Binding, 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 827)
    - NEH Training - Conservation Techniques, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 828)
    - NEH Training - Microforms, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 829)
    - NEH Training - Paper, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 830)
    - NEH Training - Yale's Program in Preservation, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 831)
    - NEH Training - Program in Preservation, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 832)
    - NEH - Travel, 1979-1981 (Box 17, Folder 833)
    - NEH Training - Deacidification, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 841)
    - No label (Candace Brugman), 1981-1983 (Box 17, Folder 842)
    - Gladis, Pat - Intern, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 843)
    - Workshops - Interns Spring 1981 (Box 17, Folder 844)
    - Planning for Preservation: CMDC Task Force, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 845)
    - RLG - Steering Committee Minutes, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 846)
    - RLG - PC Photographic Pres. Project, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 847)
    - RLG Pres. Steering Committee - General, 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 848)
    - RLG, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 849)
    - GCMPI Project Managers Meeting - New York, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 850)
    - RLG PC - Snowbird, Utah, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 851)
    - RLG PC Steering - Washington D.C., 1989 (Box 18, Folder 852)
    - RLG PC Minneapolis, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 853)
    - RLG Steering - Princeton, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 854)
    - RLG PC - Philadelphia, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 855)
    - RLG - San Francisco, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 856)
    - RLG PC Steering - Stanford, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 857)
    - RLG PC - Atlanta, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 858)
    - Northwestern RLG PC-SC, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 859)
    - Dartmouth CPMP, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 860)
    - Dartmouth PC, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 861)
    - New York PC - Steering, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 862)
    - Los Angeles PC, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 863)
    - Los Angeles CPMP, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 864)
    - New York - Steering, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 865)
    - RLG PC CPMP - Northwestern, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 866)
    - Chicago CPMP, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 867)
    - New York CPMP Costs, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 868)
    - Chicago PC, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 869)
    - Washington - Steering, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 870)
    - New York - Steering, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 871)
    - New York - CPMP, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 872)
    - Dallas - PC, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 873)
    - Washington - RLG PC, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 874)
    - Los Angeles, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 875)
    - New York - RLG Steering, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 876)
    - San Antonio PC, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 877)
    - Philadelphia RLG PC, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 878)
    - Denver PC, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 879)
    - NewYork PC, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 880)
    - Columbia University: Ad Hoc, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 881)
    - San Francisco Berkeley PC, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 882)
    - New Orleans Tulane University PC, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 883)
    - Ann Arbor University of Michigan PC, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 884)
    - AMC, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 885)
    - RLG Archives and Special Collections Task Force, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 886)
    - RLG PC - Book As Object, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 887)
    - RLG Presentation Copying, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 888)
    - RLG Music Group, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 889)
    - RLG Preservation Copy, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 890)
    - PC Resource List, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 891)
    - RLG Law Group, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 892)
    - AMSC MS. Microfilm Project, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 893)
    - RLG Art Pres. Project, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 894)
    - Coop. Microfilming Project RLG, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 895)
    - PC Training for Microfilms CBU, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 896)
    - Music Preservation RLG, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 897)
    - RLG Preservation Comm. - General, 1975-1981 (Box 18, Folder 898)
    - RLG Preservation Comm. Agenda, 1976-1984 (Box 18, Folder 899)
  - Subject Files
    - Online Catalog, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 900)
    - Optical Disc Storage, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 901)
    - OPUS (Box 19, Folder 902)
    - Overlap, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 903)
    - Pamphlets, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 904)
    - Pamphlets Binding - Intern Training, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 905)
    - Paper, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 906)
    - Paper Strengthening, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 907)
    - Parylene (Box 19, Folder 908)
    - Paper Quality - CLR, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 909)
    - PC - Steering Princeton University, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 910)
    - Pergamon, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 911)
    - Performance Evaluation (Box 19, Folder 912)
    - Permission Forms (Box 19, Folder 913)
    - Permanent Papers, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 914)
    - Pests, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 915)
    - Photo Dept Study, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 916)
    - Photocopy Licensing, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 917)
    - Photo Copy Machines - General (Box 19, Folder 918)
    - Phonodiscs, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 919)
    - Photocopying, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 920)
    - Photographic Services - Yale, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 921)
    - Photocopy Supplies, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 96)
    - Photographs (Box 19, Folder 97)
    - Photography, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 924)
    - Physical Plant, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 925)
    - Planning (Box 19, Folder 926)
    - Policies, 1978-1986 (Box 19, Folder 927)
    - Post-It Notes, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 928)
    - Preservation and Collection Management, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 929)
    - Preparation for Microfilming (Box 19, Folder 930)
    - Pres. Conferences (Box 19, Folder 931)
    - Pres. Exhibits, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 932)
    - Preservation - Developing Programs in Libraries (Box 19, Folder 933)
    - Preservation Film - CLR, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 934)
    - Preservation Graphics, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 935)
    - Preservation of Intellectual Content of Library Materials - Ch. #5 (Box 19, Folder 936)
    - Preservation Management Info. Field, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 937)
    - Pres. Microfilming (Box 19, Folder 938)
    - Pres. Microfilm Conference - ALA RLMS, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 939)
    - Preservation Medical Colloquium, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 940)
    - Preservation Planning Docs., 1985 (Box 19, Folder 941)
    - Pres. Planning Task Force - Article, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 942)
    - Preservation Programs (other than Yale), 1987 (Box 19, Folder 943)
    - Preservation Studies, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 944)
    - Preservation Talks, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 945)
    - Preservation Video Recording (Box 19, Folder 946)
    - Preservation Graphic Art - Article, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 947)
    - Previll, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 948)
    - Priorities for Preservation (Box 19, Folder 949)
    - Priveleges Fees, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 950)
    - Promotion Review Comm., 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 951)
    - Promotion Review, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 952)
    - Readex, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 953)
    - Recon (Box 19, Folder 954)
    - Recylced Paper, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 955)
    - Reference, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 956)
    - Refurbishing, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 957)
    - Reorganization, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 958)
    - Replacements / pages, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 959)
    - Reprint - Kraus, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 960)
    - Reprint - Reuquest Forms (Box 19, Folder 961)
    - Reprinters and Preservation, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 962)
    - Reprinting Contract, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 963)
    - Reprints, 1979-1986 (Box 19, Folder 964)
    - RLG, 1985-1989 (Box 20, Folder 965)
    - RLG Workstation, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 966)
    - RLIN, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 967)
    - Roger's Talk, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 968)
    - Rooms and Requests, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 969)
    - RPI, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 970)
    - Salaries / Wages, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 971)
    - SAM, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 972)
    - Scholar's Role in Preservation, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 974)
    - School and Developmental Library, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 975)
    - SCOPA, 1987-1990 (Box 20, Folder 976)
    - SCSC Internship - Marcia Watt (Box 20, Folder 977)
    - SCSC Talk, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 978)
    - SCSU Preservation Syllabus, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 979)
    - S and D Heads - Meeting and Workshops, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 980)
    - Search Tools (Box 20, Folder 981)
    - Searching Forms (Box 20, Folder 982)
    - Security (Box 20, Folder 983)
    - Se-Lin, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 984)
    - Selectors Conference SML, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 985)
    - Serials, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 986)
    - Serial Filming, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 987)
    - Signature (of books) (Box 20, Folder 988)
    - Slides - Preservation, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 989)
    - Slow Fires, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 990)
    - Software (Box 20, Folder 991)
    - Solinet, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 992)
    - Sound Recording, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 993)
    - Speakers, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 994)
    - Speeches, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 995)
    - St. Louis Conference, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 996)
    - Stack Cleaning, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 997)
    - Stack Surveys Reports, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 998)
    - Staff Education, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 999)
    - Staff News Articles, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 1000)
    - Standards, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 1001)
    - Stanford Pres. Office, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 1002)
    - State-of-the-art and Future Challenges (RGW - St. Louis), 1984 (Box 20, Folder 1003)
    - Stanford - Staffing, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 1004)
    - Stolen Books, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 1005)
    - Storage - Preservation, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 1006)
    - Supplies, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 1007)
    - Survey Article - Final (Box 20, Folder 1008)
    - Survey Info. to send out (Box 20, Folder 1009)
    - Swartzell - questions and checks with bibliographers, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 1011)
    - System Office, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 1012)
    - Tapes / Preservation, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 1013)
    - Taxes, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 1015)
    - Teams (Box 20, Folder 1016)
    - Technical Services (Box 20, Folder 1017)
    - Telephones, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 1018)
    - Teleprint (Box 20, Folder 1019)
    - Thefts, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 1020)
    - Theses - Archival Quality, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 1021)
    - Thesis Guidelines: ALA and Yale, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 106)
    - Time Estimates, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 107)
    - Time Keeping, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 1024)
    - Title IIC, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 1025)
    - Tours, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 1026)
    - Training (Box 20, Folder 1027)
    - Transfers, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 1028)
    - Travel and Expense Report Forms (Box 20, Folder 1029)
    - Travel Reports, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 1030)
    - Travel Requests, 1989-1991 (Box 20, Folder 1031)
    - Typewriters, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 1032)
    - Two week workshop - Anne (Box 20, Folder 1033)
    - Tyvek (Box 20, Folder 1034)
    - U. Conn, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 1035)
    - Union, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 1036)
    - Union Carbide, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 1037)
    - Uncataloged Hems - Binding, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 1038)
    - Univ. of Chicago (Box 21, Folder 1039)
    - U.S. Newspaper Project, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 1040)
    - U-V Screening / Filtering, 1973, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 1041)
    - Vendors (Box 21, Folder 1042)
    - Vesicular Film, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 1043)
    - Volunteers, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 1044)
    - Waechter Visit, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 1045)
    - Weeding, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 1046)
    - Wisconsin (Box 21, Folder 1047)
    - Workshop, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 1048)
    - Work Study, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 1049)
    - Intro. To Pres Workshop, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 1050)
    - Workshop Pamphlet, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 1051)
    - Workshop Talks (Box 21, Folder 1053)
    - Workshops, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 1054)
    - Writing, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 1055)
    - Wye Conference, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 1056)
    - Xerox Methods, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 1057)
    - Xerox Contracts / Invoices, 1987-1989 (Box 21, Folder 1058)
    - X Copier, 1986-1992 (Box 21, Folder 1059)
    - Yale - General Info (Box 21, Folder 1060)
    - Yale Preservation Paper, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 1061)
    - Yale Statistics and Info, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 1062)
    - Yale University, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 1063)
    - YUL History, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 1064)
    - YUL Newsletter, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 1065)
    - YULC, 1981, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 1066)
    - Publicity, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 1067)
    - Publicity, 1981-1982, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 1068)
    - Questionnaire (Box 21, Folder 1069)
    - Organization Charts, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 1070)
    - Preservation Planning, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 1071)
- Preservation department records, 1979-2001; Accession 2008-A-194
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2037
  - Departmental Files
    - Miscellaneous Yale publications, 1987-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Lib Tech, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Kentucky Virtual Library Project, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Kluwer Publishers, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - ISO Standards Committee, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - IPM Survey (Laura Miller), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Institute of Museum and Library Services (IMLS), 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - IBM -Stephenson, 1997 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Human Resources flyers, 1993-1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Good Neighbors, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Gift Policies, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Fumigation, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Food and Drink Policy, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Folios removal, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Folios -Sterling Memorial Library (SML) to Mudd, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Film Preservation at Yale, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Equipment requests, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Equipment and telephone inventory, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 20 - 21)
    - Annual report, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Cross training, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Collection Care Program (CCP) -gifts and endowment, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Conservation Program statistics, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Conservation Program statistics, 1996-1997; 2008-A-194-0001; 1; computer file (XLS) (Box 22)
    - Clippings and articles, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Catalog Department minutes (Acquisitions), 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Calhoun College Fellow, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Calhoun Library, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Card cases -relocate, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Cambodia Genocide Project, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Binding Study -report and followup, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Binding Policy, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Australia, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Annual report, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 37 - 38)
    - Action plan, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Administrative assistant, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Association for Information and Image Management (AIIM), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Advisory Committee on Library Policy (ACLP), 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 42 - 44)
    - Construction/renovation, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Conservation studio renovation, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Library Space Planning Committee, 1992-1999 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Renovation phase II, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Research Libraries Group (RLG) (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - Art Serials, 1991-1999 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      - Digital preservation survey, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 51)
      - Digital Image Capture Group, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Preservation Support Group, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Project X, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 54 - 55)
    - PJX implementation, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - PJX payroll training, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Northeast Document Conservation Center (NEDCC)
      - Advisory Committee, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 58)
      - 1998 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 59)
      - 1999 September 24 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Newspapers, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - NOS (not on shelf) replacements, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Numismatic move -Meyer, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Ornithology IMLS, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - PMT, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Society of American Archivists (SAA) leadership list, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Security and keys, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Standing Committee on Professional Awareness (SCOPA)
      - Forum, 1998 December 10 (Box 2, Folder 68)
      - Proposal, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Southern Connecticut State University (SCSU)
      - Intern, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 70 - 71)
    - SML orientation, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Space puzzle, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - SML stack survey, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - South African archivist, 1999 May 27 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Travel, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Technical Services Management Group (TSMG)
      - Planning Retreat, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 77)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 78 - 80)
      - Agenda, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Ulysses Project, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - UMI -Early English Books, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - University of Texas intern, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - University of Toronto -User Study Conference, 1997 October (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Video Archives, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Video teleconferencing, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Walpole -environment, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Web Administrators Group, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Yale Daily News, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Microfilm Inventory project, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Microfilm Unit - analysis of demand for duplication and preservation services, 1989-1996 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Mellon Intern 8, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Conservation Program, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Conservation Studio, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Core Program Issue, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Basic Program (including microfilm), 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - 1998 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - 1997 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Mass deacidification, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Psalms of David, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Binding -Art and Architecture, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Performance evaluations, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Librarian-in-Residence, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Association of Research Libraries (ARL) News, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Special assignment, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Digitization conference, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Replacements -SML/Cross Campus Library (CCL), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Tercentennial Open House 21 Oct 2000, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Microfilm -bibliographic control, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - NEDCC/Heritage Preservation, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Room 5 renovation, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - PMT, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Digital Advisory Working Group (DAWG) planning, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - NELINET (New England Library Information Network) Preservation Summit, January 2001, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - AIIM, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - AIIM Expo, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - ARL Survey Analysis, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Special Collections Initiative, 1978-1998 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Digital Rosetta Stone, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - SCOPA presentation, 2001 May (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Collection Development Council (CDC) presentation on digital Preservation, 2001 June 8 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - American Library Association (ALA) Preservation Policy, 2001 June (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Endeavor, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Library Management System (LMS) migration, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Ex Libris, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Information Conservation, Inc. (ICI) binding proposal, 2000 May (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Migration Management Group (MMG) -Endeavor, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Stack cleaning, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Action planning, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Library Management Committee (LMC) budget, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - DAWG, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - New acquisitions -Preservation, CDC, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Library Shelving Facility (LSF) files [previously known as Off-Campus Shelving Facility (OCSF)]
    - Questionnaire, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Selector Forum
      - 1997 August (Box 4, Folder 136)
      - 1998 May (Box 4, Folder 137)
      - 1998 October (Box 4, Folder 138)
      - 1999 May 6 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Selection -Working Group Report, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - CDC -Off Campus selection, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Processing manual, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Processing (final), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Processing, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Coordinators, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Harvard Depository information packet, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - Systems and Procedures Exchange Center (SPEC) Kit 242:, 1999 May (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Harris Environmental Systems, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Project Manual OCSF, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Project Manual for New Music Library at SML, vol. 2, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Environmental history (photocopies of articles from 1823-1987), Circa 1995 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Environmental science, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Planning - background, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Disaster, Circa 1990s (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Heating, ventilation, air conditioning (HVAC) background, 1992-1999 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - Facilities, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - American Historical Association (AHA) article, 1996 September 15 (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - Clean, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Preservation, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - HVAC, 1995-1998 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - HVAC standards, 1990-1995 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Renovation specifications, 1994-1997 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Conservation Analytical Laboratory (CAL) reports, circa 1996 (Box 4, Folder 163 - 164)
  - Grant Projects
    - NEH, 1979-1981 (Box 5)
    - Western Americana Preservation Project, 1994-1996 (Box 6)
    - Western Americana Preservation Project, 1994-1996 (Box 7)
  - Project Open Book (Box 8–19)
  - Project Open Book (Box 9)
  - Project Open Book (Box 10)
  - Project Open Book (Box 11)
  - Project Open Book (Box 12)
  - Project Open Book (Box 13)
  - Project Open Book (Box 14)
  - Project Open Book (Box 15)
  - Project Open Book (Box 16)
  - Project Open Book (Box 17)
  - Project Open Book (Box 18)
  - Project Open Book (Box 19)
  - Travel/PLC
    - 1992-1996 (Box 20)
    - 1997-2001 (Box 21)